<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yinxuan Fu</title>
    <link>https://fustinose.github.io/</link>
    <description>Personal website of Yinxuan Fu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 10:59:33 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fustinose.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://fustinose.github.io/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://fustinose.github.io/about/</guid>
        <description> I study at.. Carnegie Mellon University  Pittsburgh  I have worked at..  ByteDance   Shanghai 
 TalkMeUp Inc.   Pittsburgh 
I have done..  Ray  -- I like..  Music  
 Video Games  
 Reading  
 </description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://fustinose.github.io/cmu/bscs/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://fustinose.github.io/cmu/bscs/</guid>
        <description>Some Academic History I went to Shanghai Foreign Language School until 2015. I then went to Cranbrook Schools at Bloomfield Hills, Michigan, where I found my initial academic interests: Cognitive Science. I therefore applied and began my college in Psychology.
Still, CMU was renowned for its computer science program. After taking some introductory courses to programming (why not), I found greater pleasure in coding. I decided to switch to the School of Computer Science, and here I am.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://fustinose.github.io/misc/games/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://fustinose.github.io/misc/games/</guid>
        <description>My Life with Video Games I played my first video game when I was about 4 years old. It was on my dad&amp;rsquo;s old GameBoy, and I believe it was a street fighter game. When PSP first came out, my dad bought me one, and since then my life was flooded with video games.
I later (around middle school) came to know Dota2, and through it I gradually switched to computer games (good job Gabe Newell).</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://fustinose.github.io/misc/music/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://fustinose.github.io/misc/music/</guid>
        <description>My Musical History I started to listening to songs since kindergarten. I remember rocking alongside Jay Chou&amp;rsquo;s and David Tao&amp;rsquo;s songs on my way to and back from school. During middle school, I developed an interest in rock bands, and explored many artists from the 60&amp;rsquo;s to the 90&amp;rsquo;s. Later on in high school, I got exposed to Japanese music and fell in love instantaneously. I am particularly fond of band music (not necessarily rock bands), because I love drumbeats and basslines.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://fustinose.github.io/misc/reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://fustinose.github.io/misc/reading/</guid>
        <description>  What I Read I mostly read fictions, though it is very hard to describe why I like fictions. My favorite writers are Murakami Haruki and Milan Kundera, but unfortunately I do not possess the linguistic talent to read their works in the original language.
 Some of My Favorites Murakami Haruki:
 1Q84 Killing Commendatore The Wind-Up Bird Chronicle  Milan Kundera:
 The Book of Laughter and Forgetting The Joke The Unbearable Lightness of Being  </description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://fustinose.github.io/work/bytedance/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://fustinose.github.io/work/bytedance/</guid>
        <description>ByteDance  AI Lab, Speech and Audio Engineering I focused on the refactoring of the existing search engine which provides index and storage of audio fingerprints for almost all of ByteDance&amp;rsquo;s products. During my three-month internship and with the help from my colleagues, I designed and built the new system architecture that separates storage and computation for the purpose of cloud-nativization. Specifically,
 I designed and implemented a virtual-consensus-based log system, achieving near 400 Append QPS for log entries of 500KB I optimized the snapshot serialization and deserialization of the in-memory index, achieving 10x speedup on GBs of data.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://fustinose.github.io/work/talkmeup/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://fustinose.github.io/work/talkmeup/</guid>
        <description>TalkMeUp Inc.  Backend Engineer Intern I had my first internship as a software engineer at TalkMeUp Inc., which was a startup company located in Pittsburgh. It was the first time I got exposed to real industry software development. We used Node.js and React to build our web-based product. My main responsibility surrounded our database. I led the design and implementation of our MongoDB collections to serve our frontend requests.</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>