<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yinxuan Fu</title>
    <link>https://fustinose.github.io/work/</link>
    <description>Personal website of Yinxuan Fu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://fustinose.github.io/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://fustinose.github.io/work/bytedance/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://fustinose.github.io/work/bytedance/</guid>
        <description>ByteDance AI Lab, Speech and Audio Engineering I focused on the refactoring of the existing search engine which provides index and storage of audio fingerprints for almost all of ByteDance&amp;rsquo;s products. During my three-month internship and with the help from my colleagues, I designed and built the new system architecture that separates storage and computation for the purpose of cloud-nativization. Specifically,
 I designed and implemented a virtual-consensus-based log system, achieving near 400 Append QPS for log entries of 500KB I optimized the snapshot serialization and deserialization of the in-memory index, achieving 10x speedup on GBs of data.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://fustinose.github.io/work/talkmeup/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://fustinose.github.io/work/talkmeup/</guid>
        <description>TalkMeUp Inc. Backend Engineer Intern I had my first internship as a software engineer at TalkMeUp Inc., which was a startup company located in Pittsburgh. It was the first time I got exposed to real industry software development. We used Node.js and React to build our web-based product. My main responsibility surrounded our database. I led the design and implementation of our MongoDB collections to serve our frontend requests. Specifically,</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>